[
  {
    "id": 92,
    "question": "Which muscle, when in spasm, will raise the iliac crest? Lumborun (hip hiker)",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "Quadratus"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "question": "Compression is least effective for producing which of the following?",
    "options": {
      "a": "relaxation",
      "b": "an effective immune response",
      "c": "assessing clients' muscle tone effective immune response"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "question": "Which muscles make up the Pes Anserine? Gracilis, Semitendinosis",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "Sartorius,"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "question": "If you massage Tibialis Anterior, which meridian are you working?",
    "options": {
      "a": "GB",
      "b": "SP",
      "c": "ST",
      "d": "KI"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "question": "Which meridian is associated with Adductor Magnus?",
    "options": {
      "a": "LR",
      "b": "KI",
      "c": "ST",
      "d": "SP"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "question": "After applying friction to a muscle, the area may become red and puffy because of which?",
    "options": {
      "a": "release of acetylcholine",
      "b": "release of histamines histamines"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": "release of histamines"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "question": "How many hours of continuing education are required for registration of your license?",
    "options": {
      "a": "30 hours",
      "b": "15 hours",
      "c": "six hours",
      "d": "none"
    },
    "correct_option": "d",
    "correct_answer_text": "none"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "question": "Shin splints would involve which muscle?",
    "options": {
      "a": "soleus",
      "b": "tibialis anterior",
      "c": "peroneus longus"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "question": "Friction is best used on which of these?",
    "options": {
      "a": "muscle belly",
      "b": "ligaments"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": "ligaments"
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "According to the generation cycle, which element should be tonified to support the deficiency? (for the 55-yr-old man with the metal problem)",
    "options": {
      "a": "earth (tonify the mother to support the deficiency)",
      "b": "fire",
      "c": "water",
      "d": "wood support the deficiency)"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  }
]